(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-08-23T22:59:36.090061",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.6-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
hololive English -Promise- 2nd Anniversary Concert Promise 2 You
アスファルト タイヤを切りつけながら
Tires tearing through the asphalt,
暗闇 走り抜ける
as I race through the darkness.
チープなスリルに身をまかせても
Even if I surrender myself to cheap thrills,
明日ににおびえていたよ
I was still terrified of tomorrow.
It's your pain or my pain or somebody's pain
誰かのために生きられるなら
If I can live for someone else's sake...
It's your dream or my dream or somebody's dream
何も怖くはない
I have nothing left to fear.
Get wild and tough
ひとりでは解けない
Unable to solve on my own,
愛のパズルを抱いて
holding close this puzzle of love.
Get wild and tough
この街で優しさに
In this city, I don't want
甘えていたくはない
to lean on soft kindness.
Get chance and luck
君だけが守れるものが
The thing that only you can protect
どこかにあるさ
is out there somewhere.
Get chance and luck
ひとりでも傷ついた
Even all alone, I will
夢を取り戻すよ
reclaim my broken dream.
ありきたりな僕の 日々を壊してくれ
Crush my ordinary days
異常なほどの刺激を 待ち望んでいたのかな
Was I craving for such extreme stimulation?
ちょっとしたそんな冒険心は 改札に吸い込まれて
A dash of such adventurous spirit gets sucked into the ticket gate...
吐き出され辿り着いた 雨降るこの街
...and spat out into this rainy city where I've arrived.
何も感じれないまま 死んでいくのは御免だ
I refuse to die without feeling anything.
終わりのその先を目指して
Aiming beyond the end.
駆け出せ Steppin' out tonight 僕らは不確かなまま
Run out, steppin' out tonight, while we remain uncertain.
輝く Steppin' out tonight 待ってるんだぜ 明日が
Shine, steppin' out tonight, tomorrow is waiting for us!
抗え Steppin' out tonight 僕らは風の中
Resist, steppin' out tonight, we are in the middle of the wind.
それでも Steppin' out tonight 追いかけてんだ
Even so, steppin' out tonight, I'm chasing after it.
So there's no looking back
また首を突っ込んで 見事に散らかしてんだ
Sticking my nose into trouble again and making a complete mess of it.
曖昧で退屈な気持ちとおさらばさ
Farewell to these vague and boring feelings.
関係ないって顔したって どこかで繋がっていて
Even if I pretend not to care, we're connected somewhere.
何度だって引き戻すと 手招くこの街
This city beckons, pulling me back time and time again.
ビリビリ痺れるような 今を生きていたいんだ
I want to live in a present that electrifies me!
極限のギリギリで行こうぜ
Let's go right to the extreme edge!
駆け出せ Steppin' out tonight 僕らは不確かなまま
Run out, steppin' out tonight, while we remain uncertain.
輝く Steppin' out tonight 待ってるんだぜ 明日が
Shine, steppin' out tonight, tomorrow is waiting for us!
抗え Steppin' out tonight 僕らは風の中
Resist, steppin' out tonight, we are in the middle of the wind.
それでも Steppin' out tonight 追いかけてんだ
Even so, steppin' out tonight, I'm chasing after it.
So there's no looking back
Inside, outside, I just wanna feel good everyday
一切合切 I just want to feel alive
Everything, all of it, I just want to feel alive!
駆け出せ Steppin' out tonight 僕らは不確かなまま
Run out, steppin' out tonight, while we remain uncertain.
輝く Steppin' out tonight 待ってるんだぜ 明日が
Shine, steppin' out tonight, tomorrow is waiting for us!
抗え Steppin' out tonight 僕らは風の中
Resist, steppin' out tonight, we are in the middle of the wind.
それでも Steppin' out tonight 追いかけてんだ
Even so, steppin' out tonight, I'm chasing after it.
So there's no looking back
Don't take your love away
You ain't heard nothin' yet, yet
Wake up, make up, bang bang!
まだ鳴り出した表示は あなた「今忙しいの」
The screen that started ringing says you: "I'm busy now"
未読のトークとラブコールも一杯で忙しない
Unread chats and love calls are piling up, so hectic
なんてまだガキね
You're such a child still
本音は言わない方がやましい
Hiding your true feelings makes you look more guilty
甘い言葉かけるよりもずっと愛しい
Far sweeter than speaking sweet words
たまらなくなるほど 求めるのをやめないで
Crave me so much you can't stand it, don't let go
キスじゃ足りなくて
A kiss isn't enough
いっそ殺して
Just kill me already
Predilection
頭を手にかざして
Put your hands on my head
Infatuation
呼吸さえ止めて
Hold even your breath
Dedication
このまま Addiction して
Addicted just like this
まだたった一口でしまい
It's over with just one more bite
Predilection
舌口をつけて
Pressing our lips and tongues together
Infatuation
そのまま飲み込んで
Swallow it whole
Dedication
すぐさま Addiction して
Instantly addicted
ほらたった一口 死ぬほど愛したいから
See, with just one bite, I want to love you to death
Don't think your love away, wait, you're nothing yet
Don't think your love away, wake up, make up, bang bang!
派手な過剰型でいい
A flashy overdose type is fine
あなたには私しかいない
You only have me
だけど過剰型足りない
But an overdose still isn't enough
私にはあなたしかいないなんて
Saying I only have you...
みんな探した この手掴んだ
Everyone searched, I grabbed this hand
まだ未練があるのね
You still have lingering regrets, don't you?
あんたはわがまま 愛と名付けて
You're selfish, labeling it as love
私排出する
And casting me out
あなたに溺れてく
Drowning in you
息苦しいくらいに
Almost to the point of suffocating
泥酔させて
Get me dead drunk
いっそ殺して
Just kill me already
Predilection
私を手にかけて
Lay your hands on me
Infatuation
キスで口塞いで
Block my mouth with a kiss
Dedication
まだまだ Addiction して
Still getting more addicted
まだたった一口で溺愛
With just one bite, pure devotion
Predilection
毒を流し込んで
Pour in the poison
Infatuation
ためらいなど捨てて
Throw away all hesitation
Dedication
すぐさま Addiction して
Instantly addicted
ほらたった一口 これで終わらせないで
See, with just one bite, don't end it like this
Ah love, ah love... Continue to further evolve more, yeah
My love, my love... Is decided with you!
Your love, your love... Continue to further evolve more and more, yeah!
I'm a little confused!
これがあんたの本心？
Is this your true intention?
あんたはどう？ 私は？
How about you? What about me?
ふたりはただ愛されたかっただけだったの？ 私は？
Did the two of us just want to be loved? What about me?
いらない
I don't need it
そういう言葉は期待するだけ無駄だって
Expecting anything from such words is useless
私知ってしまった
I ended up learning that
理由が分からないのね
You don't know the reason, do you?
たまらなくなるほど 求めるのをやめないで
Crave me so much you can't stand it, don't let go
キスじゃ足りなくて
A kiss isn't enough
いっそ殺して
Just kill me already
Predilection
あなたを手にかげて
Laying my hands on you
Infatuation
呼吸さえ止めて
Hold even your breath
Dedication
このまま Addiction して
Addicted just like this
まだたった一口でしまい
It's over with just one more bite
Predilection
舌口をつける
Pressing our lips and tongues together
Infatuation
そのまま飲み込んで
Swallow it whole
Dedication
すぐさま Addiction して
Instantly addicted
サヨナラ真っ赤 吐き出しで息が止まるのよ 今
Goodbye, spitting red, my breath stops now
Life Will Change
It's not a game
I'm not a robot AI challenging you
I'm not a phantom
I'm in your face and
I'm here to see it through
Right before your eyes
Watch us multiply
Come to claim our rights - it's time
As our power grows
Tryin' to stop us shows
Might as well go try'n stop time
So you know that we're out there
Swatting lies in the making
Can't move fast without breaking
Can't hold on or life won't change
And our voices ring out, yeah
Took the mask off to feel free
Fought it out in the debris
Now we know that life will change
Ain't it a shame
I'm not a figment of your ailing old mind
I'm just as real as
I'm just as dangerous
As you, so know you'll find
A taste of your own meds
Fire in every breath
Fire inside your head, your heart
And as your crippled brain
Tries to fight in vain
Your empire will fall apart
And you'll know we were out there
Swatted lies in the making
Your empire for the taking
Can't hold on or life won't change
And our voices rang out, here
Took the mask off to feel free
Fought it out in the debris
Now we know that life will change
X-encounter
[Song: X-encounter]
飛べない... ここからじゃ
I can't fly... not from here.
横顔眺めてるだけじゃ
Just watching your profile from afar,
無力さを嘆いても
even if I lament my helplessness,
この背を誰も押さない
no one will push me forward.
Going out!
飛び方を忘れていた
Having forgotten how to fly,
闇鴉たちの嘆きのvoice...
the lamenting voices of dark ravens...
凍てつく無機質な
In this freezing, emotionless
世界に何を望むの？
world, what do you hope for?
そうだけどね 確実な
That's true, but a certain
希望がもう僕の中に
hope is already inside me.
Going up!
「何が出来るか」なんてもう
Asking "What can I do?"
やってみなきゃワカラナイ
is useless unless I actually try.
走り出した序章へ
Toward the preamble I started running to,
きっと生まれる前から決まっていた
it was surely decided before I was born.
羽根を揺らし強く地を蹴って
Flapping my wings, kicking off the ground hard,
君の元へ
toward where you are.
羽ばたく "RAVENS!"
Flapping wings, "RAVENS!"
Fight! Keep holding on!
何千のループの中出逢う
Meeting through thousands of loops
この現世で
in this present world.
もう止められない宿命の真下で
Beneath this unstoppable fate,
僕に出来る事がどんなにわずかでも
no matter how little I can do,
その体に背負うもの
what you carry on your shoulders...
強く飛び立つ今 恐れを
Strongly taking flight now, fear...
無傷にすり替える 自分の居場所探して
Swapping it out to leave unharmed, searching for a place to belong,
後悔になぞらえた 虚構の
likened to regret, in a fiction...
陰惨 蝕む夜にいた
...that was corroded by tragic darkness.
不器用に風に揺れて
Clumsily swaying in the wind,
僕はまだ 弱いままで
I am still as weak as ever.
迷って 壊れては
Lost, breaking down time and again,
そうやって続く世界で
in a world that continues on like this,
たった一つ 見つけたら
if I find just one thing,
また瞬く星を描き進め
I will forge ahead, drawing twinkling stars again.
闇から覗いた光
The light peeking through the darkness—
手を伸ばして さあ行こう
reach out your hand and let's go.
走り出した この思い ほら
These feelings have begun to run—look,
ここからの星が 導いて
the stars from here will guide us.
染み付いている 嫌な記憶を
Carrying away the unpleasant memories
この翼で 運び出す
that have stained my mind, on these wings.
Raven, fly keep holding on
雲を切り 形のない
Cutting through the clouds, giving form
波紋を 散らして
to shapeless ripples and scattering them.
凛とした瞳に
In dignified eyes,
宿る灯火を
the dwelling flame—
くべろ 躊躇はしない
feed the fire, show no hesitation,
君はそのままでいて
just remain as you are.
向かい風に逆らい
Defying the headwind,
小さな羽広げ
spreading small wings,
目指そう 僕ら果てる日まで
let's aim forward until the day our lives end,
共に駆けて
running together.
行こう
Let's go.
誰のせいでもない涙 誇りにして さあ行こう
Tears that are nobody's fault—wear them with pride and let's go.
走り出そう 始まりへ
Let's run toward the beginning.
きっと生まれる前から 決まっていた
It was surely decided even before I was born.
羽を揺らし 強く地を蹴って
Fluttering my wings, kicking off the ground with strength,
君のもとへ
to where you are—
羽ばたこう
I will take flight.
Raven, fly keep holding on
幾重の 後悔の後
After layers upon layers of regret,
鈍く灯る この一瞬が
this dimly lit moment
永遠へ変わる
turns into eternity.
手をつなぎ そして
Join hands, and then,
世界を見に行こう
let's go see the world.
皮肉にも 僕たちは
Ironically enough, we
長すぎる夜を 潜り抜けて
pass through an all too long night
知るんだろ
and come to understand
生きることの意味を
the meaning of living.
真実へと 掲げて行こう
Let me hold it high toward the truth.
遠回り それは孤独の
Taking a detour—that was a landscape
景色にも 愛を持てた時に
of loneliness, but when I can embrace it with love,
世界はまた
the world will once again
生まれ変わる
be reborn anew.
Thank you so much for watching...
So far!
Are you guys having a good time?
Don't forget to share your comments using the...
# shown at the top right of the screen!
hashtag shown at the top right of the screen!
#Promise2U
This way! This way! #Promise2U
All right, we're currently at the Promise Hideout!
Over there! Oh my god, that is huge!
Oh my god, it's so pretty!
I got way too excited... No, don't die! Don't die!
It's so big... Hello! Is there a helicopter flying out there taking videos of us?
Now we have it! And now that we also have such a fancy stage on the rooftop as well and everything, let's turn things up with some fun variety games!
Variety games! Variety part!
Yeah, I bet you guys are probably feeling a bit tired after that intense first half of this live, right?
I'm good! I'm alive, I'm standing. We're good!
You guys seem a little tired.
To help you recover from that fatigue and tiredness, I've prepared the perfect segment for you guys.
Yes, it's called "Pleasure or Pain? Promise Foot Massage Karaoke Battle!"
What does that mean? Foot?
Each member will sing one chorus from two songs they're good at! Battle it out by total score using the scoring system!
There's also a twist! Yes, we will be singing while receiving foot massages! And how that will affect our performance or score, well, we'll see and find out together right here!
Oh yeah... Yes!
And there'll be a punishment for the losers as well, of course.
As for the punishment, the losers will have to drink this super sour geki-suppa drink! Geki-suppa juice!
Now let me show you the key item that could make or break this battle. Here's what we'll use for the first round! Tada!
It's a Foot Reflexology Mat! I've never stepped on one of these before. - I have. Oh, it's not pleasant.
Wait, so you want us to... wait, we're singing while we're on this?
Yeah, you're gonna sound amazing. We're all gonna sound amazing singing on this.
So, who's brave enough to go first?
Senpai! Senpai!
Senpai! I feel like...
You look so beautiful today.
Nothing good comes out from compliments...
As a senpai, you should show us how it's done, right? Fine, I'll go first!
Yay! I'll show you how it's done!
So IRyS, which song are you gonna sing? - I am going to sing Zankyou Sanka.
If you're ready, get on the mat! - Yes!
I get on the mat... Don't be dramatic.
Ow! It hurts! She's fine! Music, start!
始まりよ！
Here we go!
誰が袖に咲く幻花 ただ そこに藍を落とした
A flower of illusion blooms on someone's sleeve, just dropping an indigo right there.
派手に色を溶かす夜に 銀朱の月を添えて
On the night when I was flamboyantly melting colors, decorating them with a scarlet moon.
転がるように風を切って 躓くごとに強くなった
Flying against the wind as if falling over, I got stronger every time I stumbled.
光も痛みの怒りも全部 抱きしめて
Even the light, pain, or anger, I'll embrace them all.
選ばれなければ 選べばいい
Just choose if you aren't chosen.
声よ 轟け 夜のその向こうへ 涙で滲んでた
O voice, roar beyond the night over there that's blurred by tears.
あんなに遠くの景色まで 響き渡れ
Resound to that faraway scene!
何を奏でて？ 誰に届けたくて？ 不確かなままでいい
What will you play? Who do you want to reach? It's fine even if you're still uncertain.
どんなに暗い感情も どんなに長い葛藤も 歌と散れ 残響
No matter how dark the feeling is, no matter how long the conflict is, disperse into a song, echo!
痛い！
Ouch!
I can barely... I can barely bounce!
You need to get right, good!
How's your blood flow? Do you feel...
How do you... do you feel refreshed?
You look great!
All right, looks like the score is in. Shall we see the score?
Hi! This is what you got! Ta-da!
I've never... I've never gotten a score that low before!
70.161!
That's good! That's good! What are you talking about?
You know, 70, that's a...
that's a... that's a C... no, B!
That's a B! That's a B-!
B-! B-! Yeah!
Is it a B-? That's a C, that's a C-!
No, no, no, it's a B-.
Alrighty then, who wants to go next?
Senpai! Senpai! Oh, senpai じゃない.
Senpai! Senpai! Oh, not senpai.
We're from... we're from the same...
She's senpai by two hours!
Was it two hours? Yeah, I think it was two hours.
I've never heard that from you before!
Okay, I guess.
Yay! You're gonna have so much fun!
Okay, so Kronii, what song are you gonna sing for us?
I'm gonna be singing "Mousou Zei".
Yay! "Mousou Zei"!
Cuz I only know old songs! Yay!
That's great! I know that song!
Okay then, all right, please start the music! Music, start-o!
She sounds confused.
あの子もいいな あの子もいいな
That girl looks nice too, that girl looks nice too
頭の中で イイコトしてる
Doing good things inside my head
あなたは それで 満足ですか？
Are you satisfied with that?
叶えたいとは 思いませんか？
Don't you want to make it come true?
あの子でいいや あの子でいいや
That girl will do, that girl will do
妥協大好き 飲む針千本
Loving compromise, swallowing a thousand needles
あなたは それで 満足ですか？
Are you satisfied with that?
叶えたいとは 思いませんか？
Don't you want to make it come true?
納めましょう妄想税
Let's pay the delusion tax
皆様の暮らしを 豊かにするために
To make everyone's lives richer
叶えたい たい たいを現実に
Turn your "I want it, want it" into reality
今 未来 未来 未来を買い戻せ
Buy back the future right now
アレしたい したい 病も 欲しがりも
The disease of wanting to do that, and greed too,
さあ 痛い 痛いの その向こうへ
come on, go beyond the pain
そう 汚い妄想は 汚いお金で解決させましょう
Yes, let's solve dirty delusions with dirty money
yeah!?
Oh, you did... you did amazing! Wow!
I feel like that brought out like a roughness!
Oh wow, blood circulation! That's a lot of blood circulation!
All right, the score is in. Let's see what Kronii got!
Yay!
Wait wait, it's still first half! I can still make it! I can still make it!
All right! I'm up next! Yeah, let's go!
I'm excited! I've been wanting to sing this song for so long!
Okay, what song is it? What are you singing?
Fairytale -Yakusoku no Hi-!
Finally! I finally found an instrumental track. I'm so excited!
Your childhood, I'm assuming?
Not really, no. Not really? Okay! Nice Fairytale!
Now that you're ready, please hop onto the foot reflexology mat.
Don't fail me. Ready? Yeah.
Okay, now please start the music! Music, start-o!
フェアリーテイル この手で 掴んだ光は
Fairytale, the light I grabbed with these hands...
痛い！
Ouch!
夢に描いた理想郷 夢のまま終わらせない
The utopia drawn in my dreams, I won't let it end as just a dream
いつか会える 未来の僕に 伝えたい
I want to tell my future self whom I'll meet someday
時に未来は残酷で 鏡のように割れるけど
Sometimes the future is cruel and shatters like a mirror, but
欠片を失くさないよう 見つけ出せばいい
So as not to lose the pieces, we just have to find them
凍える闇が 僕たちの 行く手塞いでも
Even if freezing darkness blocks our path,
きっと忘れない 希望
we surely won't forget hope
フェアリーテイル この手で 掴んだ光は
Fairytale, the light I grabbed with these hands...
絆の力 溢れているから
...is overflowing with the power of our bonds
Because the power of our bond is overflowing
だから 譲れない 揺るがない
So I won't yield, I won't waver
僕らは知っている 悲しい涙を
We know sad tears
だから 譲れない 揺るがない
So I won't yield, I won't waver
夢見たあの日に そう 辿り着くまで
Until we reach that day we dreamed of
You guys can sing on this thing!
It brings out something from deep within...
Since you have something deep within, it's time to see what score that brought you!
Woah, she got an 81.434!
Currently in 1st place is Hakos Baelz with an 81.434 points. Any comments heading into the second half now?
Currently in 1st place is Hakos Baelz with 81.434 points. Any comments heading into the second half now?
I'm excited! I'll continue to do my best so that I don't have to do the juice! 頑張るぞ！
I'm excited! I'll continue to do my best so that I don't have to drink the juice! I'll do my best!
All righty then, let me introduce the next key item or should I say person for the second half...
...in this foot massage battle, yeah? では、お入りください。どうぞ！
...in this foot massage battle, yeah? Now then, please come in!
こんにちは！
Hello!
Let me introduce you guys to Takita-san, who will be giving us foot massages, a foot massage pro!
よろしくお願いします。
Nice to meet you.
怖い！ 怖いね...
Scary! It's scary...
痛いですか？ 痛いです。
Does it hurt? It hurts.
Okay, so it's gonna hurt! Who wants to kick things off?
All right, since I went last last time, I'll go first this time.
What are you gonna sing?
I'm gonna be singing "Bakamitai"! 行きます！
I'm gonna be singing "Bakamitai"! Here I go!
Okay then, please get ready! 滝田さんもよろしくお願いします！
Okay then, please get ready! Takita-san, please take care of her!
優しくしてください...
Please be gentle...
怖い！ 大丈夫、健康にいいんだから。 It's good for your health!
Scary! It's fine, it's good for your health. It's good for your health!
Let's go!
Okay then, please start the music! スタート！
Okay then, please start the music! Start!
Inner peace... Inner peace... Inner peace...
馬鹿みたい 子供なのね
What a fool I am, so childish
夢を追って傷ついて
Chasing dreams and getting hurt
嘘が下手なくせに
Even though you're terrible at lying
笑えない笑顔みせた
You showed a smile that couldn't even laugh
I love you も ろくに言わない
You barely even say "I love you"
口下手でほんまに不器用
Awkward with words, truly clumsy
なのに なのにどうして
And yet, and yet, why...
サヨナラは言えたの
...were you able to say goodbye?
だめだね だめよ だめなのよ
It's no good, no good, it's no good
あんたが好きで好きすぎて
Because I love you, love you way too much
どれだけ強いお酒でも
No matter how strong the alcohol is
歪まない思い出が 馬鹿みたい
My memories won't fade, I'm such a fool
先生！ 先生！ ありがとうございます！
Sensei! Sensei! Thank you so much!
That was a beautiful ending to that song.
That's scary, oh my god!
All righty, how was that? How was the song while getting a foot massage?
I can't feel my big toe!
Now the score is in, let's see what you got! じゃじゃーん！
Now the score is in, let's see what you got! Ta-da!
You got a 68.057! It's over 50, so close to a good number, yeah!
痛っ！ ありがとうございます！
Ouch! Thank you very much!
健康になった！ You became a bit healthier!
You became healthier! You became a bit healthier!
Is it really that bad? Oh my god! You're not exaggerating, are you?
嘘じゃない！
I'm not lying!
やってみてよ！
Try it out!
I wanna try!
Okay! Before you sit down, what are you gonna sing?
I'm gonna sing...
Usseewa!
All righty, please get ready.
Takuta-san, よろしくお願いします。
Takuta-san, please take good care of her.
よろしくお願いします！
Please take good care of her!
ガチ痛い、ガチ痛い！
It actually hurts! It really hurts!
I'm a little...
You're done, you don't have to worry!
Yeah! Okay, let's go!
Start the music!
I wonder if it's gonna be that bad...
正しさとは 愚かさとは
それが何か見せつけてやる
What is rightness? What is foolishness?
I'll show you what they are!
Yeah, she seems fine! She's slowly warming up.
ちっちゃな頃から優等生
気づいたら大人になっていた
Ever since I was little, I was a model student
Before I knew it, I had grown up
ナイフの様 な思考回路
持ち合わせる訳もなく
Not that I ever had
a knife-like mind or line of thinking
でも遊び足りない 何か足りない
困っちまうこれは誰かのせい
But I haven't had enough fun, something's missing
I'm at a loss, and it's somebody's fault
あてもなくただ混乱するエイデイ
Just aimlessly confused every single day
それもそっか
最新の流行は当然の把握
経済の動向も通勤時チェック
Well, I guess so
Staying up to date on trends is a given
Checking market trends on my commute
純情な精神で入社しワーク
Joining the company with a pure heart and working
社会人じゃ当然のルールです
These are obvious rules for working adults
はぁ？
うっせぇうっせぇうっせぇわ
あなたが思うより健康です
Huh? Shut up, shut up, shut the hell up!
I'm healthier than you think
一切合切凡庸な
あなたじゃ分から ないかもね
You're so utterly mediocre,
maybe you just don't get it
鳴呼よく似合う
その可もなく不可もないメロディー
Ah, how well it suits you,
that completely unremarkable melody
うっせぇうっせぇうっせぇわ
頭の出来が違うので問題はナシ
Shut up, shut up, shut the hell up!
We're built on different levels, so no problem at all
So how was the massage?
I feel so good! Yeah!
え？ マジ？
Huh? Really?
All righty, then the score's in again.
Let me see what you got!
Result... お願いします、ジャジャン！
Results... please, da-dan!
Yeah! She got 77.994! That's literally 78! So good!
All right, well... who's left?
We only have one person left!
IRyS-san!
はい、はい。行きなさい、早く！
Yes, yes. Go on, hurry!
What song are you singing?
I am going to be singing Akuma no Ko,
because the world is just that cruel.
世界は残酷です。
先生、もう本当に思い切りやってください。
The world is cruel.
Teacher, please really give it your all.
優しくしてください！
Please be gentle with me!
いやいや、強く！強く！
No no, hard! Hard!
All right, you ready? I'm scared.
Yes! Music start!
Oh man, my heart's beating.
鉄の弾が 正義の証明
貫けば 英雄に近づいた
An iron bullet is proof of justice
Whenever I shot, I drew closer to being a hero
その目を閉じて 触れてみれば
同じ形 同じ体温の悪魔
If you close your eyes and touch it
It's a demon with the same shape and body heat
僕はダメで あいつはいいの？
そこに壁があっただけなのに
Am I no good while he's okay?
There was just a wall standing there
生まれてしまった 運命嘆くな
僕らはみんな 自由なんだから
Don't lament the fate of being born
Because we are all free
鳥のように 羽があれば
どこへだって 行けるけど
If I had wings like a bird
I could go anywhere, but...
帰る場所が なければ
きっとどこへも 行けない
If I have no place to return to
I surely can't go anywhere
ただただ 生きるの は嫌だ
I hate the thought of just living
世界は残酷だ それでも君を愛すよ
The world is cruel, but I still love you
何を犠牲にしても それでも君を守るよ
No matter what I sacrifice, I will still protect you
間違いだとしても 疑ったりしない
Even if it's a mistake, I won't doubt it
正しさとは自分のこと 強く信じることだ
Righteousness means believing in yourself strongly
How do you feel? Was it refreshing?
Refreshing, right?
It was great!
素晴らしい体験をさせていただきました。
I had a wonderful experience.
All right, I feel like the scores are in!
Shall we see?
ジャジャン！
Da-dan!
77.716! You did so good!
And that concludes the second half!
My big toe still hurts so bad! - I know!
みんな痛がってました、Takuta-san.
Everyone was in pain, Takuta-san.
ありがとうございました！
Thank you very much!
痛気持ちよかったです。
It hurt, but it felt good!
ありがとうございました！ バイバイ！
Thank you very much! Bye-bye!
Okay then!
I present to you
the final scores!
The one and only first place
with 151.858 points is...
Ouro Kronii!
How do you feel? How do you feel?
Oh, I wish I got a massage for my left side too. That would have been so nice.
But you know, I'm so happy that we got to suffer together!
Yay!
Okay, now with that wholesome moment aside...
Yeah! Let's get back to the live!
Not yet. Not yet.
Wait, actually, yeah, let's get back to the live! Yeah!
Yeah, I think it's time, yeah.
It's time for the punishment game!
Staff-san, please prepare.
Thank you, thank you.
Okay, so today's is like a super sour drink?
Yeah, I heard it's a sour drink.
It smells healthy.
Oh wait, it smells good though.
It smells like ass.
It's like... like ume? It smells like ume.
Yeah, it doesn't smell bad.
じゃ、不健康の2人で
Well then, for the two unhealthy ones,
乾杯！
Cheers!
That sounds wonderful.
梅！
Plum!
That's actually really good.
Really? Wow!
Are you good?
Yeah, it's good... It's actually great.
It tastes better after a bit more time.
My face is turning into that lemon meme, you know?
That face just inverting...
Yeah, but...
I feel sour, but probably healthy.
Healthy, guys! That's healthy!
Okay, so we're going to return to the live performance,
and the second half includes new songs,
so let's keep it going, guys!
Woohoo! Yay!
Let me go back in!
Ah, you guys are fine, okay, let's get a move on.
Let's just... let's just get a move on.
All right. Okay.
You still... really? I'm fine now.
だいぶ、だいぶ良くなったよ
I've gotten much, much better now.
ぜんぶ ぜんぶ あんたのせいだ
It's all, all your fault.
ヘドが出るくらいに うざったいわ
You're such a pain, it makes me wanna hurl.
何かすがって へつらって
Clinging to things, fawning over things...
期待したあたしが 馬鹿だった
I was stupid to think I'd get something out of it.
ご機嫌伺いの 方方嬰人
I'm a people-pleaser coming to pay my respects,
それゆえにアンチな 一生義務
so gimme a hater life.
浅いキャパシティ 毎度おおきに
I've got a shallow capacity, thanks for your patronage.
詰まるとこ人生 ずっと地味
Basically, my life's always been drab.
「憎々しい！」 「痛々しい！」
"How hateful!" "How pathetic!"
無視できないのがいっそう
The way I can't ignore you makes it worse -
腹正しい イライラしい
How maddening, how vexing.
そろそろあきたじがじさんに
I've had just about enough of blowing my own horn.
(look around!!)
ライクの反対はアパシィ
The opposite of like is apathy
＝繋がれた証
≈ proof that you're connected.
切り離せない関係
A relationship I can't cut off...
逸らしてしまう対話
I'd love to just look away from it.
これはいわゆるヘイトスピーチ
This is what you'd call hate speech.
匿名性の生命を 生命に乗せてんだ
We're posting these anonymous declarations onto our very lives.
鳴りやまないサイレン 近付くたびに痙攣
We spasm every time those ceaseless sirens draw near.
赤信号にずっと順従です
We've obeyed red lights all this time.
だいたいあんたのことあたし
Point is, I absolutely -
ダイダイダイダイダイキライ
- hate hate hate hate hate you.
OMG情けない もはや
OMG, how pathetic, I just wanna say -
バイバイバイバイバイしたい
- bye bye bye bye bye already.
脳内も予測不能ゆえに
Can't tell what's going on in that mind, and thus there's -
カイカイカイカイカイはない
- no no no no no solution.
どうだい？あたしのことあんた
How's it? Do you absolutely -
ダイダイダイダイダイキライになった？
- hate hate hate hate me now?
ああ百害あって一利
Ah, all pain and no gain,
なし Nothing not see
nothing, not see.
もしたらればなべてもニコチンだし
It'd be like nicotine to think back on the what-ifs.
I miss youって千回言った
Going back because I missed you
結末はボンミスボンミス
was a stupid mistake, mistake.
せんきゅう半面教師
Thanks for being a great bad example.
あと味一生消えてくんないわ
You've left an aftertaste that won't ever disappear.
よしよしいい子ね
There, there, what a good girl.
笑顔振り撒きパラパラいい子ね
Strewing your smile around, scatter scatter, what a good girl.
だけどだけどその本性は？
But you know, but you know, what's your true nature?
善悪の区別もつかないの？わらはあ。
Can you even tell right from wrong? (lol) sigh.
減点方式で取り巻く
Shrouded by an environment
環境に撒かれて
that traps people with demerits.
紹介、痛い！痛い！痛い！
"Ow! Ow! Ow!" you cry,
もう聴き入れ言わない！って
"but no one asks!" you'll say for life, but -
当然の報いに食らっちゃった
serves you right.
人は鏡なのです
People are mirrors.
実のところ依存です
The truth is, it's codependence.
シャットダウンしても付きまとう
Even if you shut it all down, it still sticks around.
煽れの弱さがふがいない
My weakness feels so cowardly.
ぜんぶ ぜんぶ あんたのせいだって
It's all, all your fault I say.
ヘドが出るくらいに...
It won't stop, it makes me wanna hurl...
解んないわ
...I don't even get it...
いっそのこと切り離す方が楽なのに... なー！
It would be easier to just cut ties... right?!
大体アナタのことアタシ ダイダイダイダイダイキライ
Basically, I super duper duper extra hate you!
お前が情けない 最早バイバイバイバイバイしちゃっ
You're so pathetic, I just wanna say bye-bye-bye-bye-bye...
の脳内も予測不能ゆえに
...and because your mind is so unpredictable...
カイカイカイカイカイは無いくらい
...there's hardly any resolution at all.
どうだい？アタシのことアナタ ダイダイダイダイダイキライになった？
How about it? Have you come to super duper duper extra hate me too?
アァ百害あって一利ナシ
Ah, all harm and zero benefit,
nothing not see
nothing to see,
もしたられば並べてもニコチンだし
even if you list all the "what-ifs", it's just like nicotine.
i miss youって近付いた
You approached saying "I miss you",
結末は凡ミス凡ミス
but the ending was just a silly blunder, a total mistake.
センキュー反面教師
Thank you, bad role model,
後味一生消えてくんないわ
the aftertaste won't disappear for the rest of my life.
Oh
Uh-huh
Yeah
I'm not interested in what you want.
I'm the real special in this world.
H-A-L-F
簡単な英語しかわかんない
I only understand simple English
踊るの大好き 健康第一
I love to dance, health comes first
憧れとコンプレックス 大渋滞
Longing and complexes in a massive traffic jam
カーステでノリノリ
Grooving with the car stereo
カーストは飽き飽き
Sick and tired of the caste system
試されてる いつもいつでも
Being tested, always and forever
恵まれてるかどうかを
Determining whether I'm blessed or not
楽しくしていたい 泣きたくないから
I just want to have fun, 'cause I don't want to cry
問いただす 神様がいなくても
I'll question it, even if there's no God
もうカッコつけてくしかないじゃん
There's no choice but to keep acting cool, right?
そのまま このまま 降り注ぐ光ね
Just as it is, just like this, the light pouring down
半分なんて思ったことないぜ
I've never thought of myself as just half
このまま そのまま 突き進む光
Just like this, just as it is, the light pushing forward
いじわるなんかじゃ止まんない
A little malice won't stop me
笑わせたいのに上手くできない
I want to make you smile, but I can't do it well
誰かのせいにはしたくないよ
I don't want to blame it on anyone else
生まれてみたいから生まれてきただけ
I was only born because I wanted to be born
新しい普通としあわせ
A new kind of normal and happiness
そんなに遠くはないでしょう
It shouldn't be that far away, right?
それでも今も誰かが
Even so, right now someone is still
打ち放つ かなしみと怒りの
Unleashing sadness and anger
H A L F
損をしたり ちょっとつらい
Taking a loss, feeling a bit down
そんな日もあるけど
There are days like that too, but
茨の道で花が咲くなら
If flowers bloom along a thorny path
絶対見逃せない
I definitely can't miss it
もうカッコつけてくしかないじゃん
There's no choice but to keep acting cool, right?
そのまま このまま 降り注ぐ光ね
Just as it is, just like this, the light pouring down
半分なんて思ったことないぜ
I've never thought of myself as just half
このまま そのまま 突き進む光
Just like this, just as it is, the light pushing forward
X.U.
I don't want nobody to get killed
I'll come and get you, I am always ready to fight
So don't take all of the blame, we're all swept away
Don't take all of the weight, you always do
There will always be something you cannot control
We will overcome, your salvation has begun
No signs, no lights, such a mess all over
Don't kill your hopes
You make me realize who I need
I'll be there, hold on
They'll change you somehow
So where are you now?
I'll reach you by dawn
Before you can be turned
Illusions are torn
The fallen angels you run with don't know
It is our pain that makes us all human after all
Warm old sepia photographs show
Our fragile precious world
Must protect it, respond to the call
Are they really deep inside your head?
Do they control you like a little marionette?
I'll cut the strings off you dead, come in with me
Let me free the wings of your soul, can make it fly
We've been waiting here just to make you whole again
No more hating, see, I have always been your friend
No signs, no lights, such a mess all over
Don't kill your hopes
You make me realize who I need
I'll be there, hold on
They'll change you somehow
So where are you now?
I'll reach you by dawn
The shadows appear
Illusions are born
The fallen angels you run with don't know
It is our pain that makes us all human after all
Torn old sepia photographs show
Our fragile precious world
Must discard it, respond to the call
If you wanna fight with me
Then go ahead and fight with me
'Cause all I wanna do is help you, man
You will be the death of me
The power of our army has been cut with a scythe
And if we lose you to them, we may never survive
You can leave, but you must first believe
Just one step at a time and keep your head up, boy, and
You'll be free
Yay!
How was that so far?
That was good! How do you feel?
Feels good!
Do you guys like how it's been going so far in the songs?
Do you guys like how it's been going so far with the songs?
Yay!
We just had all of our solo songs...
Yeah!
...and we also went through the variety part, and...
...and everything, yeah!
How are you guys doing? Still hurts?
I don't know how I danced this way!
I don't know how I danced like this!
How are you guys? You're probably fine.
No, no!
You're fine! I'm not worried about you at all. How about you?
My foot still hurts, but it's okay!
Yay! Persevere!
There's a surprise at the end, but before that...
Oh!
...we have an announcement about merchandise! Check this out!
Woo! I love the key visual!
Yeah! It's the Hololive English Promise 2nd Anniversary Celebration merch!
We're releasing merchandise to commemorate our 2nd Anniversary!
Let's take turns introducing the merch, shall we?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah!
Oh! Oh!
So first up is a Frame Art Board of our wonderful key visual for the Promise 2nd Anniversary!
The frame part uses luxurious, sparkling paper,
and the printed illustration turns this into a high-quality piece of art!
Oh my!
You definitely don't want to miss the chance to add it to your collection or room!
And guess what? You can even hang it on the wall!
Oh my god, on the wall?! On the wall!
Next up are the Collection Cards for each of Promise!
These cards feature an attractive design that are foil stamped on the front,
and you can choose each card individually,
so be sure to collect all of them!
Gotta collect them all! Wow!
Next!
Next, we also have Ring Necklaces!
Woo!
Yeah! This design includes key references and motifs for each of us!
You can use it as either a ring or a necklace,
so feel free to change it up depending on the occasion!
Woo! Next!
And next, we have special porcelain Tumblers with our designs on them!
It features our talent colors on top of a black base.
They're designed to have a unified look,
and I bet it'll look so cool if you use several of these tumblers together
in like a drinking party or something!
Yeah!
Okay, last one!
And lastly, we have a 2-WAY Tote Bag!
It's a two-way design that can be used as both a shoulder bag and a tote bag!
Ooh, that's actually really cool!
It's even designed to be used as a carry-on bag too,
perfect for traveling and convenience!
And to top it off, it has many pockets that will definitely be useful
for storing small items like other merch!
Woah! Yeah! Cute!
Oh my god!
Yes, and that concludes the Promise 2nd Anniversary Merch...
...introduction!
Please check it out! 楽しみに心待ちにしています！
Please check it out! We're looking forward to it!
And with that, we're finally at the very last part.
Aha!
Sorry for keeping you guys waiting.
We mentioned that there'd be a special, you know, surprise or announcement earlier.
Would you like to hear what it is?
Yes! Yeah!
I wonder what it is.
Oh, but before that...
But before we announce it,
it's time for a stage change!
Stage change! Woah!
Wait, wait, wait! What's going on? Oh my god, we're floating!
We're going up, we're going up! No!
Oh, god! Everybody keep--
No, I'm fine! No, wait, wait!
No, don't rush!
Okay, okay, okay, we good, we good.
Okay, okay, okay, we're good, we're good.
I'm getting claustrophobic!
I'm gonna be sick!
It's opening! I see the light!
Oh, my goodness.
Nice. Oh, that's nice. I feel fresh air.
All righty. Well, ladies, it is time for our final announcement!
Final announcement?!
We, Promise, have a new original song!
Finally releasing! It's called "Run Back 'Round"!
Out right now! Look at that!
We worked really, really hard on this song. And it's really cool, really catchy. It's quite different to...
...you know, a lot of the original songs that Promise has put out before, so...
Different genre.
A different genre.
Yeah! We hope that you guys will listen to it a lot. The chorus part is quite hype...
...and honestly quite easy to remember, so I feel like, you know...
...hopefully it becomes an earworm, and you can put it on loop over and over and over again!
That's our big reveal!
So exciting! I'm so excited!
Well, I think the only thing that's left is for us to perform our new song!
What?!
We're gonna perform it here?! Here?! Floating in the city?!
But before we go, do you have any final thoughts about our live, about our anniversary?
I am just super happy we got to do this. This is Promise...
...and, you know, it was a lot of fun singing all those songs with you guys, you know, different duets.
And I just really like the fact that we have a hideout now.
We do! We have a hideout now! Yeah!
Our two-year anniversary celebration...
...and it's in a fabulous location! Imagine how expensive the rent is!
Management's gotta pay for it. We'll pay for it. Okay.
So, yeah, I'm really happy. How about you guys?
Yeah, I'm just really thankful that, you know, we're still here after two years...
...and, you know, hope everyone continues to support Promise. Thank you guys! And here's to many, many more!
Yay!
I could say the same thing. I'm just gonna steal everyone's and say that it's been great being with all of you...
...for two years. And, you know, now we get to have this cool hideout...
...and this awesome song that we get to show everyone. So, yeah!
Yay!
We ready? Yeah, I'm ready.
Are we ready? Yeah, I'm ready.
Let's go! Ready...
...set, go! Run Back 'Round!
Run back 'round...
Don't stop now...
Up with the moonlight,
Down in the streetlights,
Looking for a spotlight,
Making my move
Whoa
I'm running
行こう
Let's go
Days like a whirlwind,
don't stop coming,
Got me in a tailspin,
What can I do?
Whoa
Keep running
行こう
Let's go
Lost and found,
back to where I started,
I won't stay down,
trust me, I can do it!
I live life loud,
take it to the limit,
So stand up proud,
now I'm gonna sing it!
Run back 'round, it's a new beginning,
I run back 'round, got to keep believing,
I run back 'round, I know where I'm going,
I run back 'round, nothing's gonna stop me now!
Woah, oh, oh!
I'm gonna run back 'round!
Sparks on the pavement,
Dreams in the distance,
Gotta be relentless,
Faster than sound.
Whoa
Keep running
行こう
Let's go
Oh yeah...
Lock it and load it, 僕らは explosive
Lock it and load it, we are explosive
Swifter and lighter, 明日もきっと brighter
Swifter and lighter, tomorrow will surely be brighter
Oh yeah...
Faster than lightning, about to get exciting
Keep on running...
Run back 'round, it's a new beginning
I run back 'round, got to keep believing
I run back 'round, I know where I'm going
I run back 'round, nothing's gonna stop me now!
Woah, oh, oh!
I'm gonna run back 'round!